// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What comes next in the series: 3, 6, 9, 12, ___?",
    answer: "18",
    options: [
      "15",
      "18",
      "21",
      "24"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which shape is missing from the pattern: ▲ ▲ ▲ ▼ ▲ ▲ ▲ ___?",
    answer: "▼",
    options: [
      "▼",
      "▲",
      "■",
      "●"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " Fill in the missing number: 2, 4, 8, 16, ___.",
    answer: "32",
    options: [
      "24",
      "32",
      "48",
      "64"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the next letter in the sequence: A, C, E, G, ___?",
    answer: "I",
    options: [
      "H",
      "I",
      "J",
      "K"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "If 'book' is to 'reading' then 'fork' is to ____?",
    answer: "eating",
    options: [
      "eating",
      "food",
      "kitchen",
      "cooking"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

   {
  numb: 6,
  question: "Complete the analogy: Sun is to day as moon is to ____?",
  answer: "night",
  options: [
    "night",
    "star",
     "sky",
    "dark"
  ] },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "If 'run' is to 'ran' then 'sing' is to ____?",
    answer: "sang",
    options: [
      "sung",
      "sang",
      "singed",
      "sings"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "If 'circle' is to 'round' then 'square' is to ____?",
    answer:"corner",
    options: [
      "sharp",
      "triangle",
      "rectangle",
      "corner"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "If all bloops are razzies and all razzies are lazzies, then are all bloops definitely lazzies?",
    answer: "yes",
    options: [
      "yes",
      "no"
      
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Mary's father has five daughters: 1. Nana, 2. Nene, 3. Nini, 4. Nono. What is the fifth daughter's name?",
    answer: "Mary",
    options: [
      "Nunu",
      "Mary",
      "Lisa",
      "Nina"
    ]
  },

];